Guide to the Schickel family papers, 1905-1965
Schickel family papers, 1905-1965
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Schickel family papers, 1905-1965.
3671
Schickel family
15.1 cubic ft.
Financial Records, Manuscripts, Correspondence, Legal Documents
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Schickel family papers include correspondence, applications, a housing survey, inquiries and replies, licences, patents, financial records, payroll, blueprints, drawings, specifications, advertisements, brochures, trade catalogs, contracts, orders, political letters, progress reports, and other records pertaining to the business interests of Norbert H. Schickel, Sr., particularly relating to his involvement in Ithaca, New York housing and real estate development, engineering, investments, and the family owned motorcycle manufacturing company, Schickel Motor Co. Personal papers include bills, a broadside, theses, correspondence, income tax and insurance records, maps, notes, diaries, legal papers, and photographs of the Schickel family.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Schickel family papers include correspondence, applications, a housing survey, inquiries and replies, licences, patents, financial records, payroll, blueprints, drawings, specifications, advertisements, brochures, trade catalogs, contracts, orders, political letters, progress reports, and other records pertaining to the business interests of Norbert H. Schickel, Sr., particularly relating to his involvement in Ithaca, New York housing and real estate development, engineering, investments, and the family owned motorcycle manufacturing company, Schickel Motor Co. Personal papers include bills, a broadside, theses, correspondence, income tax and insurance records, maps, notes, diaries, legal papers, and photographs of the Schickel family.
Among the persons represented are Assemblyman Ray Ashbery, Charles H. Blood, Professor Alan Bloomberg, Dale Carnegie, Leigh M. Champaign, D. Boardman Lee, Rocco P. Lucente, Robert V. Morse, Gerald P. Schickel, Norbert H. Schickel, Jr., Ruth M. Schickel, William Schickel, and Allan H. Treman. Also reprsented are the American Society of Mechanical Engineers; Catholic Youth Organization; Chemung Valley Home Builders Association; Cornell University; Corning Glass Works; Fairview Manor; Federal Housing Administration; General Electric; Grange League Federation coop; H. A. Carey Co., Inc.; Immaculate Conception Church; various City of Ithaca offices, including the Planning Board and the Real Estate Board; Ithaca Chamber of Commerce; Ithaca Journal; Montgomery Ward; National Association of Home Builders; New York State Home Builders Association; United States Departments of Commerce and Patents; and other organizations involved in manufacturing, engineering, banking, insurance, real estate, and housing.
Also, "Schickel Family Memoirs," by Agnes Schickel Anderson, 1987, including photographs and copies of letters; "A Pictorial Narrative of the Schickel Motocycles, 1907-1924," by Kenneth E. Anderson, 1989; and "Schickel Family Genealogy Recordkeeper," compiled by Agnes Schickel Anderson, 1990.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Schickel family.; Anderson, Agnes Schickel.; Anderson, Kenneth E.; Ashbery, Ray Stevens, 1902-1974.; Blood, Charles Hazen, 1866-1938.; Bloomberg, Alan.; Carnegie, Dale, 1888-1955.; Champaign, Leigh M.; Lee, Douglass Boardman.; Lucente, Rocco P.; Morse, Robert V., 1888-1966.; Schickel, Gerald.; Schickel, Norbert H., 1886-1960.; Schickel, Norbert H.,; Schickel, Ruth M.; Schickel, William.; Treman, Allan H., 1899-1975.; American Society of Mechanical Engineers.; Catholic Youth Organization.; Chamber of Commerce (Ithaca, N.Y.); Chemung Valley Home Builders Association.; Cooperative Grange League Federation Exchange.; Cornell University.; Corning Glass Works.; Fairview Manor.; General Electric Company.; H. A. Carey Company.; Immaculate Conception Church (Ithaca, N.Y.); Ithaca (N.Y.). City Planning Board.; Ithaca (N.Y.). Real Estate Board.; Montgomery Ward.; National Association of Home Builders (U.S.); New York State Home Builders Association.; Schickel Motor Co.; United States. Dept. of Commerce.; United States. Federal Housing Administration.; United States. Patent Office.
Titles:
Ithaca Journal.
Subjects:
Engineering.; Housing.; Housing surveys.; Mechanical engineering.; Motorcycles.; Motors.; Ithaca (N.Y.)
Form and Genre Terms:
Accounts.; Blueprints.; Diaries.; Patents.; Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Personal papers may not be used, cited or quoted without permission of the donor.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Series I. Business Records
Series II. Series II. Miscellaeous Records
Series III. Series III. Schickel Moter Co. Records
Series IV. Series IV. Personal Papers
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Business Records
  - A - misc., Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - A. B. C. Steel Equipement Co., Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - A & T Wrecking Co., Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Abbott, Mrs. G. Harry, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Abrams Aerial Survey Corp., Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Abstract of Title, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Accountants Supply House, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Acme Tile Co., Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Adams, Dr., Provost, Cornell University, to request for purchase of Unversity Property on Oak Avenue, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Addresses, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Adhesive Products Corp., 1956 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Aerocrete Corporation of America, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Agency Tile & Supply Corp., Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Agency Tile & Supply Corp., Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Agoston, Eugene J., 174 W 70, NYC, Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Agrico-American Agri. Chemical Co., 1959 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - airborne Computor Laboratory - Owego, Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Air Photo Supply Corp., 1959 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - ALCO Valve Company Inc., Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Alderman, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Allen Communications, Inc., The, 1950-1954 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Allen, Fay E., Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Alliance Realty Corp. Lincoln-Alliance Bank Bldg., Rochester, NY, Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Aluminum Company of America, 1946-1954 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Aluminum Flake Company, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Aluminum Panel Walls See also Alum. Co. of America, General Bronze Corporation, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Aluminum Window Corp., The/General Bronze Corp., Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Ameigh, Manley, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Ameigh, Manley, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - American Appraisal Co., The, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - American Automobile Assn., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - American Brass Company, The, 1949-1954 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - American Concrete Institute see also box file, Undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - American Concrete Institute, The, Undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - American Floor Surfacing Machine Co., Undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - American Hammered Piston Ring Co., Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - American Hard Wall Plaster Co., 1949-1954 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - American Inst. of Management, Undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - American Motorists Ins. Co., Undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - American Motorists Insurance Co., McKinney Agency, Inc., Undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Original photocopied guide was illegible for this entry - title is approximate
  - American Motors Corp., Undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - American Photocopy Equip. Co., 1945 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - American Photocopy Equipment Co., photocopy machine Correspondence and Instructions, Undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - American Planning and Civic Association, 1950-1954 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - American Polytec Corp., Undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - American Radiator & Standard Sanitary Corp., 1954 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - American Rock Wool Corporation, Thermafiber Perimeter Board, Undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - American Society for Testing Materials, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - American Society of Heating and Ventilating Engineers, 1946-1954 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - American Society of Mechanical Engineers, Undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - American Society of Mechanical Engineers, Undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - American Society of Mechanical Engineers, Undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - American Society of Mechanical Engineers, 1953-1957 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - American Standard Assn., Inc., 1957 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - American-Standard Radiator & Sanitary Corp., 1954 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - American Standards Association, Inc., 1954 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - American Steel and Wire Co., Undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - American Warming & Ventilating Co., Undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Amsterdam Co. see Advertising Novelties, Undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Anchor Concrete Products, Inc., 1954 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Anderson Co., J. M., Undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Anthracite Industries Ass'n., Undated (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Anthracite Marble & Tile Co., Undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Antoni, C. M., Undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Apollo Metal Works, Undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Appelson Paper Products, Undated (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Applications, Job, Undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Applications, Job, Undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Applications for Secretarial Position, 1946-1954 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Architectural Forum, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Architectural Forum, Undated (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Arco Metal Craft, Inc., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Arco Metalcraft, Inc., L. Marder, Undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Armitage, Clinton, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Armstrong Cork Products Company, Undated (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Artcrete Products, Undated (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Artisan Metal Products/Waltham, Mass., Undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Arvedson, G. C., Undated (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Arwitz, Bernard, 1951-1954 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Ascher, Mr. Sam, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Ashbery, Ray. Assemblyman, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Associated Gas and Electric Co., Undated (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Asso. for the Help of Retarded Children, The, Undated (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Athenia Steel Co., Undated (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Atlantic Refining Company, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Atlantic Tug and Equipment Co., Inc., Undated (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Atlas Ball Company, Undated (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Atlas Plywood Corp., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Auburn Button Works, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Auburn Mattress Factory, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Aurex New York, Inc., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Automatic Reclosing Circuit Breaker Co., The, Undated (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Aviation Surplus Center, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - B - misc., Undated (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Backner, Edward, Undated (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Bagnardi, J. Victor, Undated (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Bahr, John J., Undated (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Bailey, S. J., Undated (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Bailey Meter Company, 1950-1954 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Baker Lumber Co., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Bank of New York, Undated (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Bannon, F. M., M.D., Undated (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Barber-Coleman Co., 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Barney Moravec Inc., Undated (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Barnhart Co., A. W., 1958 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Bartlett, Albert E., 1954 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Bartlett Mortgage & Bond Co., Undated (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Bauer, Catherine, 1948-1954 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Beach Refrigerator Co., Undated (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Beals McCarthy & Rogers, Inc. general correspondence, 1949-1954 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Beathan, Mark, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Beebe, Mrs., Undated (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Bell & Gosset Co., Undated (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Belmont Smelting & Refining Works, Inc., Undated (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Bendix Household Appliance Co., Undated (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Bendix Products Corporation, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Ber1an Window Shade Co., Inc., Undated (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Berns, W. F., 1959 (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Bethlehem Steel Co., 1929-1930, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Better Homes & Gardens, 1947-1954 (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - Bickford Brothers Co., Undated (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Bielen, Steve, Undated (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Bird, Donald, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Bishop and Babcock Mfg. Co., Undated (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Black Company, John H., Undated (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Blake Specialty Co., Undated (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - Blood, Charles H., Undated (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - Bloomberg, Prof. Alan, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - Blystone Co., F. M., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - Blysone, M. E./Elmira, Undated (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - Board of Education, Undated (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - Bohn Aluminum and Brass Corporation, Undated (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - Boket and Co., H., Undated (Box 1, Folder 133)
  - Book of the Month Club, Undated (Box 1, Folder 134)
  - Borg-Warner Corporation, 1955- (Box 1, Folder 135)
  - Bostwick, C. D., Undated (Box 1, Folder 136)
  - Bostwick Steel Lath Co., Undated (Box 1, Folder 137)
  - Botwinik Brothers, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 138)
  - Bowlzer & Co., D. H., Undated (Box 1, Folder 139)
  - Bowman, Inc., George A., Undated (Box 1, Folder 140)
  - Boynton, Ben V., Undated (Box 1, Folder 141)
  - Brabant, P. W., & Co., Undated (Box 1, Folder 142)
  - Bradt, Clarence G., 1949 (Box 1, Folder 143)
  - Brady, William E., Chairman, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 144)
  - Bresee, Rev. H. N. Elmira, Undated (Box 1, Folder 145)
  - Bridgeport Brass Company, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 146)
  - Briggs Manufacturing Co., Undated (Box 1, Folder 147)
  - Bristol, Maurice E., Jr., Undated (Box 1, Folder 148)
  - Broms, Prof. B., 1959 (Box 1, Folder 149)
  - Brooks Brothers, 1949-1954 (Box 1, Folder 150)
  - Brooks, Richard F., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 151)
  - Broome Distributing Co., Undated (Box 1, Folder 152)
  - Browlow, George W., Jr., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 153)
  - Bruce Co., E. L., Undated (Box 1, Folder 154)
  - Bruno-New York Inc., 1954 (Box 1, Folder 155)
  - Brydges, Earl W., Chairman, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 156)
  - Building Commissioner - Borough of Manhattan, Undated (Box 1, Folder 157)
  - Bukowy, Conrad, Undated (Box 1, Folder 158)
  - Bureau of Municipal Research & Pennsylvania Economy League, Undated (Box 1, Folder 159)
  - Bureau of Professional Regis. [tration], Undated (Box 1, Folder 160)
  - Burgess, Harry R., Undated (Box 1, Folder 161)
  - Burgess Seed & Plant Co., 1944 (Box 1, Folder 162)
  - Burghardt, Mr. Edward, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 163)
  - Burns, Franklin L. see also Real Estate Development, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 164)
  - Burns Realty Company, Undated (Box 1, Folder 165)
  - Burroughs Adding Machine Company, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 166)
  - Burton, John. Ch. NY State Pow. Comm., Undated (Box 1, Folder 167)
  - C - misc., Undated (Box 1, Folder 168)
  - Camp Barton Associates, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 169)
  - Camp Co. Inc. - Latex Concrete, Undated (Box 1, Folder 170)
  - Canavan, Richard J., 1958 (Box 1, Folder 171)
  - Carbide & Carbon Chemicals Corp., Undated (Box 1, Folder 172)
  - Carborundum, Undated (Box 1, Folder 173)
  - Carey Co., Inc., H. A., Undated (Box 1, Folder 174)
  - Carey Co., H. A., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 175)
  - Carey Co., Inc., H. A., Undated (Box 1, Folder 176)
  - Carey Co., Inc., H. A., Undated (Box 1, Folder 177)
  - Carnegie, Dale, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Carpet Company, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Carr, Lewis Bruce, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Carruthers, E. H., Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Carter, Mr. John/19 South Baker Hall, Ithaca N.Y., Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Cascadilla School Development Fund, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Case, W. A., & Son Mfg. Co., Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Case, W. A., & Son Mfg. Co. (Sinks)/Binghamton, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Casterline, Mr. G. S. - NY Board Fire Underwriters, Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Catholic Activities Com. K of C, 1955- (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Catholic Activities Com. K of C, 1948-1954 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Catholic Youth Activities Ithaca, NY, Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - C.Y. O. [Catholic Youth Organization], 1947-1954 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - CYO Card Party Committee, Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - CYO Entrance at K of C, Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Celotex, 1946-1954 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Central Trust Co., 1946 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Chain Store Business Guide, Inc., 1958 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Chambers Corporation, The, Undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Champaign, L. M., Undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Champaign, Leigh M., Undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Champion Sheet Metal Co., Inc., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Charter & Ordinance Committee, Undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Chase Brass & Copper Co., Undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Chem Industrial Co., Undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Chemung Foundry Corporation, Undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Chemung Valley Horne Builders Assoc., Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Chemung Valley Horne Builders Assoc., Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Chicago Pump Company See Sewerage Disposal Plants, Undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Chrysler Corp., 1955 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Chrysler Corporation, 1955- (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Churey, John H., 1957 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Ciaschi, Theresa, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Circulars, Undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - City Electric Company, Inc., Undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - City of Ithaca, Undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - City of Ithaca, 1946- (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - City of Ithaca - Chamberlain's Office, Undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - City of Ithaca - Building Commission, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - City of Ithaca, Building Commissioner, John A. Lunn, Undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - City of Ithaca re Elmcrest Circle, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - City of Ithaca Planning Board, 1954-1959 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - City of Ithaca Planning Board, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - City of Ithaca, Dept. of Public Works, 1954, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Clarborne, E. L., 1955 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Clarey, B. M. Rep. of H.B.A. of Finger Lakes, Inc. see also H.B.A. of Finger Lakes, Inc., 1958 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Clark McKibben & Co., 1942 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Clark's Elastic Porcelain, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Clausen, Robert T., 1950-1951 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Clauson, Frank A., 1953 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Cleartex Co., 1955 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Clifton Springs Sanitarium & Clinic, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - C1ynes, James J., 1958 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Coal, Undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Cohn-HaIl-Marx Co. see Plastic Strips, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Cole, Honorable W. Sterling, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Coleman, Francis J., 1961 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - College of the Sacred Heart, 1933, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Collier, H. C. & Sons, Inc., 1959 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Collum Acoustical Co., Inc., 1953-1954 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Columbia Graphs, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Colorcrete Industries, Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Colorcrete Industries, Inc, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Colorcrete, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Comet Boat & Class, 1946- (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Commercial Press, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Commercial Travelers Mutual Accident Assoc. of America, 1950-1954 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Committee of Engineering Laws see also NYS Soc. Of Prof. Eng., 1954 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Comptroller, Mr. Morris S. Tremaine, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Congress of the u.S. House of Representatives, 1951-1954 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Congress of the u.S. Senators & Representatives, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Connecticut Mutual Life Ins. Co., 1943 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Connecticut Valley Mfg. Co., 1949-1954 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Consolidated Mach. & Sp. Co. Ltd., 1951-1954 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Construction Machinery Co., 1950-1954 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Contact Aeration Co., 1954 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Container-Craft Inc., 1955 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Contempora Products Co., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Continental Casualty Co., 1959 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Controller State of NY, Mrs. J. V. Graham, Mgr. Mortgage Div., 1950-1954 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Convent of the Sacred Heart (Kenwood), 1937 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Conver Steel & Wire Co., 1955 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Cook, Ivan E., Mayor, 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Coop. & C Family Foods, Inc., Undated (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Cooperative Consumers' Soc. Inc., 1947-1954 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Cooperative G.L.F. Exchange, Inc., 1948-1954 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Cooperative Playschool Assoc., Undated (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Copease Company, 1953-1954 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Copeland, Mrs. Morris A., Charter Revision Commission, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Corbin Screw Corp., 1930-1932 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Cornell Theatres, Inc., 1946-1954 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Cornell University, 1941-1963 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Cornell University Alumni, 1949-1959 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Cornell University Alumni, Supt. Bldgs. & Grounds, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Cornell School of Engineering, Prof. H. H. Schofield, 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Cornell Fund, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Cornell Dean E. H. Litchfield, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Dept. of Eng., 1954 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Cornell Graduate School, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Cornell Soc. of Eng., Undated (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Corning Glass Work, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Corning Glass Center, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Corp. Statement, Bank Statements, etc., Undated (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Cortland Wholesale Electric Co., 1941 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Cotex Corp., 1933 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Cotton-Hanlon, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Cowell, Dr. Edward H., 1942 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Coxhead, Ralph C., Corp., 1946 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Credit Bureau of Ithaca, Inc., 1955 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Crosta, Joseph, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Cuddy, George J., Auburn(Door Closers), 1939 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Cummings & Lockwood, 1928-1942 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Cummings & Lockwood, 1936-1942 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Cutting Motors, Undated (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - "D" Misc., Undated (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Davis Appliance Co., 1951 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Desco Vitro Glaze, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Detmold, Mabel, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Detroit Lubricator Co., 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Detroit Stamping Co., 1926, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Detroit Steel Products Co., 1936-1938 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - DeWalt Products Corp., 1936-1948 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Diederiche, Prof. Herman, 1933-1936 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Diesel Engines - De La Vergne Machine Co., 1926 (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - "D" Misc., Undated (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Dietzgen, Eugene, Co., 1928, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Dillon, w. C. & Co. Inc., 1947 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Director of Internal Revenue, 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Dole Valve Co., 1928, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Domestic Engine & Pump Co., 1935-1936 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Donnelley, Reuben H., Corp., 1936, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - Drake, Claude also Ralph, Undated (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Dresser & Escher, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Driscoll Bros. & Co., 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Dropkin, David, Computations for Heating System for Small House, 1946-1954 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Dunbar Bros. Co., 1929 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Dyas, Richard C., D.S.S. Credit Corp., 1954 (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - "E" Misc., Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Eastman Kodak Co., 1953, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Eclipse Machine Div., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Edge, Stanley, Market Analysis, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Elastic Porcelain Lining Corp., 1961, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Elaterite Paint & Mfg. Co., 1939 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Eljer Co., 1938, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Elm Street House, 1941-1947 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Elm Street House, 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Elmira Bank & Trust Co., 1939 (Box 3, Folder 10)